索纳监狱是条不归路
Sona's a one-way street
进去了
What goes in
就再也别想活着出来
never comes out.
自从去年暴动后
Since the riots of last year,
他们就管不了我们了
they lt here us to rot.
他们以为我们会自取灭亡
They figured we would just destroy ourselves,
然而我们却日益强大
but instead we've thrived.
我们合作吧
How about we work together, you know,
一起逃出去
help each other out?
你自谋生路吧
You're on your own.
把我弄出去
Get me out of this You want to know
你要想知道她在哪
where she is, find a way
就想办法把我弄出去
to get me out of this
玛丽克鲁兹 玛丽克鲁兹
Maricruz Maricruz.
我们能帮助你 你是否考虑下
We can assis you should you ever decide,
再 越狱
say, to break out of here.
谈话到此为止
This conversation's over.
我们想让事情简单点
We're trying to do this the easy way.
能帮个忙么?
Think you can do me a favor?
林肯 我们有很多话题好谈的
We have a lot to discuss, Lincoln.
尤其是 关于你弟弟
Specifically, your brother.
转狱的事办的怎样了?
How are we coming with the transfer?
你得留下
You got to stay.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
爸爸 对不起
Dad, I'm so sorry.
他们抓了我和莎拉
They got me and Sara.
你有一周时间来找这个惠斯勒
You got a week to find this Whistler guy.
否则的话 他们都会死
Otherwise, they, uh, both die.
你从哪来 兄弟?
Where you from up there, bro?
芝加哥
Chicago.
迈克尔 乔丹
Michael Jordan.
是
Yeah.
见过他么?
You meet him?
地方太大了(见不到)
It's a big city.
哦 是啊 大城市来的
Oh, yeah, big city.
谢谢你给我留了个位
Thanks for saving me a spot.
嘿
Hey
走开
Ejected
你搞过金发的拉拉队员么?
You ever have sex with blond cheerleader?
是的 当然了
Yeah, sure.
真有你的 兄弟
You're the man, bro.
断水多久了?
How long's the water been out?
自从去年暴动
Since riots last year.
政府责怪我们
Government blame us.
他们说 该死的 你们自作自受
They say,"Screw you, you break it."
然后就没水了
No water.
谢谢
Gracias.
真够快的
Real quick.
这里有个人叫詹姆斯 惠斯勒
There's an inmate here named James Whistler.
我要找他
I'm looking for him.
欢迎加入
Welcome to club.
人人都在找他
Everybody looking for him.
为什么?
Why's that?
他杀了巴拿马市长的儿子
He killed the mayor of Panama City's son.
在一次酒吧斗殴中
In bar fight.
市长很生气
Mayor not happy.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
那他在哪呢?
So where is he now?
人间蒸发了
Disappear.
有人甚至说他逃出去了
Some say he might even escape.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey
我没钱
"I don't have no money.
我没钱 光听到你讲这个
I don't have no money,"that's all I hear from you,
你知道么?
you know that?
现在让我看到了吧?
But then I see you with this, huh?
生活有滋有味么
Life must be good, eh?
我真的很饿
Look, I'm-I'm hungry, okay?
那我就不饿了么
You worry about me being hungry.
嘿 嘿 嘿 别这样
Hey, hey, hey,hey, come on.
别这样
Come on
但是你整天都有吃的
But you eat all the time.
在那上面 我都看到了
Okay, I can see you up there.
嘿 冷静点
Hey, tranquilo
还会有水的
There's gonna be more water.
什么时候?
When?
我说了还会有的
I said there will be more water.
什么时候
Whew
走了 兄弟
Later, bro.
走
Go.
能给我点么?
Spare a little?
我需要点消息
I need some information.
当然可以
Absolutely.
你昨天把这塞进我裤袋里
You slipped this note in my pocket yesterday.
为什么?
Why?
渴的厉害 有点记不清了
My memory's a little foggy on account of this thirst.
有点回忆起来了
Yeah, it's starting to come back to me now.
再一点 就全记起来了
A little more agua there.
纸条
The note.
有个家伙 给了我点鼠肉
This guy gave me some rat meat in exchange for putting that
让我把这个塞进你和你对手的口袋里
in your pocket and the pocket of the guy you were set to fight.
为什么?
Why?
他是个疯子 这就是原因
He's nuts, that's why.
能住在下水道这种地方的人
Anybody who can live down in those sewers
总是有点不太正常
doesn't have all his faculties.
在下水道的什么地方?
Where in the sewers?
惠斯勒
Whistler
Whistler.
我叫 迈克 斯科菲尔德
My name is Michael Scofield.
我来这把你弄出去
I was here to get you out of here.
我想他们已经告诉你了
I'm going to assume they told you I was coming.
告诉你有人要来
Or that someone was coming.
惠斯勒
Whistler.
最后的机会
Last chance.
我不会再来这了
I'm not coming down here again.
你关在这 就为了助我逃出索纳监狱
You're here to get me out of Sona.
你很惊讶吗?
Are you surprised?
只是觉得要从这逃出生天
It's just that it's gonna be a bit difficult
有点困难
getting me out of this hole.
如果我从这里走出去
Seeing as if I go above ground
会有狱友盯上我
and another inmate spots me,
我就死定了
I'm a dead man.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
最新最快字幕下载请登录：www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：梁良
我和市长之间有些
There's a, there's a slight misunderstanding
有些小误会
that I have with the mayor
我不关心这个
You know what? It's none of my business.
时机成熟 我就回来带你走
I'll come back and get you when the time is right.
应该花不了多久
I may not make it that long.
那是你的事了 我的朋友
That's your problem, my friend.
我也有我自己要处理的事
I've got problems of my own.
你为这些家伙卖命?
So you work for these people?
就是为那些希望我出去的人
The ones that want me out of Sona.
听着 你别随便乱跑就行
Look, just stay put.
因为根本没人知道你在这儿
As long as no one knows you're here,
所以你应该很安全
you should be safe.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
他们为什么迫切希望我出去
至少给我透露下吧
can you at least tell me that?
你用这招装无辜?
Is this the part where you pretend you're innocent?
整件事情都是走卒一个?
Just a pawn in all this?
如果他们之前和你说任何关于我的事
If they told you anything about me before you came here,
你应该明白是真的
you'd know that to be true.
我只不过是想知道他们到底想要什么
I just want to know what they want with me.
呆着 别离开
Stay put.
为了节省时间
In an effort to save some time,
我还是要强调下
I'm gonna have to insist
跳过那段我们都明白的
that we just skip right past all the threats I know
事先准备过的威胁论
you're prepared to layout.
要是莎拉和LJ有什么三长两短
Should anything happen to Sara to LJ,
你会追我到天涯海角
you will scour the Earth and hunt me down
抽我的筋 扒我的皮
and rip my heart from my chest
之类的 等等
and bup, bup, bup.
我绝对明白你的感受
I absolutely know how you feel,
就这些 行吗?
as would I, okay?
那就这么说好了
So that's done.
来谈正事
On to business.
你弟弟收到口信了吗?
Did you brother get the message?
很好 我们每天都会在这里碰头
Good. You and I will meet here every day.
我需要一份详细的越狱进展
I'll want a full report of the prior day's progress.
我打你手机 你就接听
When I call your cell phone, answer.
别问我傻问题
Don't ask me stupid questions.
别浪费我时间
Don't waste my time.
整体计划好
Get a plan together.
然后去执行
Execute it.
拿惠斯勒来换LJ和莎拉
LJ and Sara will be traded for Whistler.
明白?
Are we clear?
我要儿子和莎拉的照片 证明他们没事
I want a picture of my son and Sara to prove they're alive.
没问题 我来搞定 还有呢
Fine. I can do that, next.
为什么选择我们?
Why us?
我会回答这个问题
I'll answer that question
这样你就能安心的做好你的工作
so we can put it to bed and you can focus on your work.
鉴于惠斯勒犯罪的性质
There's a political spotlight on Whistler
他在政界很受关注
due to the nature of his crime.
暴力解决 贿赂 随便什么招
Raids, bribes, what have you,
都行不通
are not an option.
这么说吧 只能走歪门邪道
We have to go in through the back door, so to speak.
一星期不可能搞定
This can't be done in a week.
你就只有一周时间
You have a week. That's it.
明白?
Are we clear?
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
苏珊 B. 安东尼
Susan B. Anthony.
我猜想你绝非
I'm assuming you weren't
出生于名门正派
born by immaculate conception.
林肯 你说的没错
You're right, Lincoln.
家庭成员都会受到影响
Family trees being what they are,
母亲 父亲 兄弟姐妹
moms, da, brothers, sisters.
要是我儿子和莎拉有任何不测
Anything happens to my son or Sara,
我绝不会放过你 苏珊
I'm not coming after you, Susan.
快开工吧
Get to work.
成交
It's a deal
他的人抢走了水
His man knocks over the water
难道你没见勒齐就这么逍遥地走了
Now, didn't you see how Lechero just walked away?
他根本不关心我们
He doesn't care about us
他根本屁都不管
He doesn't give a damn
高高在上 享受帝王般的生活
Living like a king up there
出来啊 你怎么了 害怕了
Come out, what are you, afraid?
来啊
Come on
勒齐 你出来啊
Lechero, come out
行个方便吧
Por favor.
求你了 行行好吧
Por favor. Vete.
滚开 臭乞丐
Vete, perro.
你为什么对下面那家伙这么感兴趣?
Why you so interested about that guy down there?
没有原因
No reason.
知识分子 那你为何这么小声
Then why you whispering, college boy?
要不要给你个扩音器啊?
Why don't you lower your voice already?
-我能有什么好处? -抱歉
-What's in it for me? -I'm sorry.
这儿除了我 你还有别的朋友吗?
Do you have any other friends in here besides me?
我就是你的好处
I'm it.
-朋友间怎会让对方挨饿 -好吧
-Friends don't let friends go hungry and thirsty -All right.
-好吧 -还有这见鬼的半裸装
-All right. -and damn near half-naked.
-我都说了 我会处理的 -什么时候?
-I said"all right. I'll take care of it -When?
当我可以的时候
When I can.
有什么大交易?
What's the big deal?
他为什么要躲起来?
Why's he hiding?
他要躲谁?
Who's he hiding from?
市长放话给勒齐说
Mayor get message to Lechero
如果惠斯勒死在索纳监狱
saying if Whistler guy gets killed here in Sona,
杀死他的人可以上庭
whoever kills him gets to go to court,
进行裁决
gets to see a judge.
和市长一起进行友善的裁决
Judge friendly with mayor.
杀了他 然后
Kill him, and-and
你就可以离开这里 获得自由?
then you get to get out of here and be free?
勒齐是这么说的
That's what Lechero say.
这是我和你之间的秘密
This'll stay between me and you.
如果你的朋友想让你知道 他干吗不告诉你?
If your friend wanted you to know, why didn't he tell you?
因为 因为你和我现在是朋友了
Cause 'cause you and I are friends now.
除非你想做敌人
Unless you want to be enemies.
我选择做朋友
Friends.
很好 我也是
Good. Me, too.
苏克雷?
Sucre?
苏克雷 请帮我离开这里
Sucre, get me out of here, please.
玛丽克鲁兹在哪里?
Where's Maricruz?
玛丽克鲁兹她很好 很安全
Yeah, Maricruz she's good, she's okay,
但是我不会告诉你任何事
but-but not telling you anything
除非你帮我离开这里
until you get me out of here.
告诉我她现在在哪里
Tell me where she is right now
你打死我 你会在这里度过下半辈子
You shoot me, you'll end up inside this hellhole.
我准备好了
I'm done.
我豁出去了
I don't care anymore.
我只能当她现在已经死了
I can only guess she's dead by now,
所以我要你去陪葬
so you're dying with her.
我没有碰过她
I never had her
在墨西哥的那个屋子里
At that house in Mexico,
我追到了你阿姨和玛丽克鲁兹
I chased your aunt and Maricruz off.
我告诉他们如果不赶快逃走的话
I told them I'd lock 'em up
我会把他们锁起来
for accessory if they didn't hightail it.
我对天发誓
I swear to God.
那个十字架呢?
And the crucifix?
是我在玛丽克鲁兹逃跑之前
I ripped it off
从她身上扯下来的
Maricruz before she ran.
这里没有电话 所以我知道
There was no phone in that dump, so I knew you wouldn't
你不能从路边打电话
be able to call from the road to
确认我没有撒谎
to make sure I wasn't lying.
我保证
I-I conned you.
所以
So
所以玛丽克鲁兹
so Maricruz is
也许在摘葡萄
She's picking grapes.
我不知道
I have no idea.
把枪放下吧
Now, just lower the barrel.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
现在 我都告诉你了 都帮到你了
Now, I came clean with you and helped you out,
对吗 兄弟
right, buddy?
所以你要报答我
So you got to return the favor.
打电话给我在茱丽叶市的妈妈 爱德娜 贝里克
Call my mom in Joliet Edna Bellick.
在电话簿上可以找到 苏克雷?
She's listed. Sucre?
我绝对没有碰玛丽克鲁兹
I never laid a hand on Maricruz.
我从没做过
I would never do that
苏克雷 请你帮帮我
Sucre, help me, please
苏克雷 帮帮我
Sucre, help me
帮帮我
Help me
你找到惠斯勒了?
You find Whistler?
是的
Yeah.
他发生什么事了?
What's his story?
我不知道 也许
I don't know, and maybe
不知道更好 对吗?
it's better that way, huh?
我只需要
I just got
帮他越狱 对吗?
to get him out of here, right?
加油 兄弟 加油
Come on, man, come on.
我们要抓紧了
We got to keep moving, we got to keep moving.
下一步的行动是什么?
What's the next play?
惠斯勒昨天放了张纸条
Whistler got a note out
在尸体上面
on a dead body yesterday.
我不知道代表什么意思 或者要给谁
I don't know what it means or who it's for.
但是我们要争取主动
But we need all the leverage we can get,
而且
and, uh
我要点钱
I need some money.
以前从来没有人从这里成功越狱
No one's ever broken out of this place before,
更不用说用一个星期来计划了
let alone with a week to plan it,
所以
so
告诉那些带走了莎拉
you tell these people, whoever it is that took Sara
和我的外甥的人
and my nephew
告诉他们我知道了
you tell them I get it,
我会尽我所能
and I'm going to do everything I can.
我会帮那家伙越狱的
I'm going to break this guy out of here,
拼死去做
or I'm going to die trying.
要是真丢了这条命
And if it's the latter,
某种程度来说也是值得的 对吗?
then that should count for something, right?
会有意义的
Th's got to count for something.
就这么告诉他们
You tell them that.
我会的
I will.
告诉他们
Tell them.
稍后我会告诉你地点的
I'd trade places with you in a second.
我知道
I know.
惠斯勒?
Whistler?
你在这里很危险
You're not safe here.
我会带你到安全的地方
I can take you someplace that is.
如果你是来帮我的
If you're here to help me,
那别管我了
then just leave me alone.
求你了
Please.
苏克雷?
Sucre?
林肯
Linc
你在这里干吗?
What are you doing here?
迈克被关起来了
Michael's locked up.
为什么?
For what?
我不知道 我正在理头绪
I don't know. I'm sorting it through.
我需要你的帮助
I could use your help.
我们 我们情况很糟糕
We're in a we're in a bad spot.
我了解你的感受 我已经脱困了 林肯
Uh, I feel for you, man, but I'm done with bad spots, Linc.
我要去见玛丽克鲁兹
I'm going to go see Maricruz.
我刚和我的堂兄皮特打过电话
I just talked to my cousin Petey,
他告诉我她回芝加哥了
and he told me she's back over in Chicago.
你在芝加哥还被通缉 记得吗?
Hey, you're still wanted in Chicago, remember?
我会想到办法的
I'll figure something out.
好吧
All right.
如果你改变主意了 我住在德赛大酒店
If you change your mind, I'm staying at the Plaza del Sol.
我不会改变主意的 我要离开这里 兄弟
I won't. I'm-I'm out of here, bro.
我要去见我女人
I'm going to go see my girl.
听我说 你生命中无辜的人
Listen to me. The innocent people in your life
你得让他们置身事外 哪怕意味着
you got to keep them innocent if that means walking away
你要离开他们 但你得这么做
from them, that's what you got to do.
祝你好运 林肯
Good luck, Linc.
请去 维莎利斯银行
Banco de Versailles, por favor.
这家伙做事真可笑
Have we had our laughs with him yet?
哥们 他一点都没用
He's useless, man.
你觉得他没用
You want to get rid of him?
是吗 那么你来削芒果
Huh? Then you cut the mango. Huh?
你今天在外面闯了
You caused me
一个大祸
a big, big problem out there today
你知道吗
You understand that?
现在断水了
Now there's no more water.
他们活得下去的
They'll live.
是吗?
Oh, yeah?
他们活得下去?
They'll live?
是吗? 要么你去告诉他们
Yeah? Well, you tell them that, then.
喂 你倒是出来啊 尊敬的先生
Hey, come out, Your Majesty.
蒂博格
Teodoro
你是不是怕见
Are you scared of
我们这些小人物啊
little people like us?
这儿有点水
There's water here.
给每个人分一点
Give each man a little, hey?
马上就去办
At once.
国王们的头被砍了
The kings have their heads chopped off.
喂 勒齐
Hey, Lechero
别替我们担心
Don't worry about us
我们没事
We're fine
他在外面是称王称霸
He may have ruled the streets
不过在这里
out there, but in here,
他其实跟我们一样
he's just like us.
跟我们一样
Just like us
出来啊
Come out
怎么了 害怕了
What, are you afraid?
出来见见我们
Come and look at me
出来
Come on
勒齐 出来
Lechero, come out.
你看到那个穿着内衣的美国人吗?
The American in his underwear you seen him?
帝博格
T-Bag.
小子 你等着喝你自己的尿吧
Boy, you're going to be drinking your own urine
这个 想都别想
before you get any of this.
我要见勒齐先生
I just need to speak to Ser Lechero, please?
我看你自己想办法吧 小跳蚤
Why don't you do yourself a favor scamper.
可是 我有一些消息 哦 是吗
But I got something. Oh, yeah.
你现在就像古印度贱民一样
You got yourself the untouchable status.
搞得老子跟你说说话就有可能招来杀身之祸
Get myself killed just talking to your mangy ass.
闪一边去
Andale
我真的有消息
But I got information.
非常重要的消息
Good information.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind, huh?
喂 喂 他有话要说
Hey Hey Hey He's got info.
把他腿敲断
Pick a pick a kneecap, huh?
我有重要的消息 我只想要点吃的和穿的
I got information I just want food and clothing.
帕顿 不要这样
Patron, please.
等下 等下
Hold on. Hold on
你的消息最好是有用的
This better be informative.
不然你的膝盖就完了
Or it's your kneecap next.
今天早上 就在那个水事件之前
This morning, before that whole, uh, water thing,
我 我听到你跟伙伴们说起
I, I heard you and the lads talking
那个叫惠斯勒的人 你们说要找到那个人
about that Whistler character, how ne's found him.
然后
Well
我想要点吃的和穿的
I just want food and clothing
说重点 笨蛋
Just tell him, idiot
有个人
There's a guy hiding
藏在下水道里
down in the sewers.
我 我猜他是不想让你发现 对吧
I-I figure he's hiding from you, right,
因为你是这儿的老大
because you run this place, right?
我估计你想知道这些
And so I figured you'd want to know everything
全部的情况 所以
goes on here, so
好了 闭嘴
Fine, shut up.
有可能是惠斯勒 是吧
It just might be Whistler, si, patron?
是吧
si?
那个人是不是澳大利亚人
Is he Australian?
是的
Yeah.
Yeah
这是勒齐的慷慨恩赐
Courtesy of the Lechero's munificence.
好了 现在你们都该支持他了吧
All right, now, y'all need to back up a tad now.
你进来多久了?
How long you been in Sona?
3年
Three years.
今年几岁
How old are you?
Seventeen.
据你所知
And as far as you know,
没人能够从这里越狱出去吧 除了
no one's ever broken out of this place except,
那个 叫惠斯勒的家伙 对吧
uh except maybe this Whistler guy?
你们美国人就喜欢问东问西的
You Americans ask a lot of questions.
噢 可恶
Oh, no.
怎么了
What's wrong?
坚持住
Come on. Please.
坚持住 我有一个家庭
Come on I have a family.
我也是
S-So do I.
坚持住
Come on.
停
Stop
停下来
Stop, okay?
可不可以
Just
他得跟我走
He's coming with me.
迈克 别过来
Just back up, Michael. Just
你不要以为杀了人
You don't actually think that killing somebody
就能帮你从这里出去
is going to help you get out of here, do you?
这的确看起来很奇怪
That does seem pretty strange, doesn't it?
因为这本来就是个奇怪的地方
But this is a really strange place,
我也很想从这里出去
one I want to get out of.
我可以帮你
Then I'll help you.
我可以证明给你看
I'll testify for you,
不管发生什么情况
whatever it takes. Wow.
看看你头上的光环吧
Wow, look at that halo
上帝在召唤你了
that just appeared above your head.
这真有趣
It's amazing.
阿历克斯 我没有选择 你昨天和我说的
I don't have a choice, Alex What'd you tell me
昨天?
yesterday?
你昨天是怎么跟我说的 你自谋生路吧
What did you tell me yesterday? You are on your own
别过来
Back up. Back up
你
You
你可不想这样
you don't want this.
我可以帮你 阿历克斯
Let me help you, Alex.
尊敬的先生
Hey, your majesty
你得干掉他
You got to shut him up.
来吧
Come on
我得靠这个大干一场
I need this bolson to call me back.
我得和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
没有我的允许
Don't ever walk in here
-就不要进来 -对不起
without being called I'm sorry.
但这值得一听
But it's worth the breach in etiquette.
现在么
Is it now?
我想你可能用的上这个忙
I thought you could use my help.
而只有我才有办法
There are ways I can be of assistance.
关于惠斯勒的
不
No.
这我可不稀罕
nothing to me, man.
我有五桩命案在身 我可没打算
I have five consecutive life sentences I ain't coming out
这么快就从索纳监狱出去
of Sona no time soon.
我为什么要抢了别人逃出去的机会呢
And why should I deprive other men of chance at freedom?
你要相信我
Huh? I need you to trust me.
哦
Oh.
相信你?
Trust you?
我对你可不放心 哥们
I don't know you good enough, brother.
蒂博格
Teodoro.
是 先生
Si, patron?
我能相信这小子么
Can I trust this bobo?
他就像条蛇
He's a snake.
每当他找到机会
He stabbed me
他就从后面咬我一口
in the back every chance he got.
在暗处咬人的蛇
A snake who stab a man in the back.
我可从没听过这种动物
I never hear of such a creature before.
我们不能再这样了
We got to stop this
再给我两分钟
Just give me two more minutes.
现在就滚
Leave now
滚
Leave
这就是你给我们的
That's what you're giving us
天哪
Your crumbs
喂 勒齐
Hey, Lechero,
你的电视怎样了
how's your television?
你的婊子呢
How's your whore?
来啊 你在怕什么
Come on, what are you scared of?
我需要些好酒
I need some, uh, some moonshine.
-好酒? -普通的也行
Moonshine? Or some alcohol.
波子酒
Booze.
对 波子酒
Booze, yeah.
我现在就要 一升或一加仑
I need it now. A liter or a gallon
只要你能弄得到就行
whatever you can get your hands on.
现在可不是聚会时间 哥们
It's not good time for party, bro.
到时带到我那去
Bring it to me in my cell.
维拉 维拉
Vera,Vera.
那女的在等你了
The woman's been waiting for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
维拉 马德里
Vera Madrid.
但愿你没等太久
I hope you haven't been waiting long.
索菲亚 卢果
Sofia Lugo.
我是詹姆斯 惠斯勒的女友
I'm James Whistler's girlfriend.
你是他帐户的签字人
You're signatory on his account.
请稍候
Wait here.
她很漂亮
She's beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
我女友怀孕了
My girlfriend's pregnant.
恭喜你
Oh,congratulations.
我准备
I'm going
需要帮忙么?
Can I help you?
不 谢谢 我没事
No thank you.I'm good.
看上去你似乎需要点什么
Cause it looked like you needed something.
不
No.
我在等车而已
I'm just waiting for the bus.
我们走吧
Vamonos.
得了吧 惠斯勒
Come on, Whistler.
你在
What are you
惠斯勒 快停下
Whistler, stop
停下
Stop
惠斯勒
Whistler
和我一起出去
Just come up top with me.
还是跟我走对你比较有利
至少你可以向勒齐申诉
At least you can plead your case to Lechero.
快
Just get
去死吧
Go to hell.
快
Just
他说这是最好的一批了
His best batch, he say.
很好
It's fine.
我还需要一些塑料袋
I'm going to need some plastic bags.
你这可不是在准备宴会
You didn't get it for to party, did you?
我要尽可能多的塑料袋
Plastic bags, as many as you can get.
不会让你白忙活的 放心
就是这个?
This is it?
是的
That't it.
能签个名么
If you could just sign for it.
谢谢
Gracias.
打扰一下?
Excuse me?
你会说英语吗
You speak English?
会
Yeah.
我们见过面的
We've met.
我的意思是我昨天在
I mean I saw you yesterday at, uh,
在索纳监狱
Sona
是的 你知道的
Yeah. You know, uh,
你可以抛开所有寡妇的伤心事
you could lose the whole grieving widow thing.
你是惠斯勒的女友 是吗
You're Whistler's girl, right?
抱歉 我还有事
I'm sorry, I have to be somewhere.
我有事要做 可以吗
I've got, uh, I got to do something, all right?
做什么
Do what?
给我
Give me that back
否则我叫警察了
or I'll call the police.
你不会叫警察的
You're not going to call the police.
他为什么想要这个?
Why does he want this?
我不知道
I don't know.
他只是一个渔夫
He's just a fisherman.
渔夫?
A fisherman?
那你告诉你的渔夫朋友
Well, tell your fisherman friend
告诉他 这个在斯科菲尔德的兄弟那
tell your fisherman friend Scofield's brother has this.
你们这些人
Why won't you people
怎么就不放过我啊
just leave him alone?
你以为我们想被迫介入这件事吗?
You think we want to be forced into this?
你以为我们想到这儿来吗 女士?
You think we want to be here, lady?
被迫介入什么?
Forced into what?
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
好的 拿住这个
All right, hold this.
拿住
Hold it.
替我看着走廊
Watch the hallway for me.
我和这儿的每个人都是朋友 兄弟
I'm friends with everybody here, bro.
这就是为什么我还活着
That's how I keep alive.
你和我是朋友 对吗
You and I are friends, right?
是的 但看起来你好像有仇人
Yeah, but looks like you got enemies.
我为你所做的 帮你弄东西
What I did for you, getting you those things
没有人会知道
No one will ever know.
勒齐 勒齐
Lechero Lechero
站起来 站起来
Stand up, stand up.
站起来
Stand up.
加油
Come on.
后退 后退
Back up Back up.
你们可以得到他
You can have him,
但你们中有两个会因此丧命
but two of you will die in the process.
你先 ?你先? 我会让你的脑袋开花
You first? You first. I'll wrap this right around your head.
靠边 靠边
Move. Move
勒齐
Lechero
勒齐 勒齐
Lechero Lechero
够了
Enough
让我下去吧
Let me go down there.
让我去解决一个
Let me cut just one throat.
就一个
Just one.
之后又会重新组织起来
And then regroup later
有理有据地
with a real reason
你给我闭嘴
to come after you. Shut your mouth.
他是对的
He's right,
山姆
Sammy.
勒齐 勒齐
Lechero Lechero Lechero
那么我们要怎么做 老板?
So, what we going to do, boss, huh?
只是坐在这里
We just going to sit up here,
希望他们把所有的石头都用完?
hope they run out of rocks?
勒齐 勒齐
Lechero Lechero
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
什么麻烦
What is it?
没水了
Ran out of water.
那么 你的意思是你们遇到问题了
So, you mean you've got a problem.
看看吧 这儿发生骚乱了
Look, there was an accident here.
装水的桶被人打翻了
The tank tip over.
我的人需要水
My men need water, man.
我尽力看能不能让储水车 后天到你们那儿
I'll see if I can get the water truck there day after tomorrow.
不 我们现在就需要水
No, I need water now
那真是太遗憾了
I guess it's too bad there's no guards
没警卫管你们了 是吧?
in there anymore with you, huh?
你可以
You could
挟持人质 制造暴动 下达命令
take hostages, have a riot, make demands.
就后天
Day aftertomorrow.
勒齐
Lechero
你要是再以这种语气给我打电话
You call me and you raise your voice at me like that
那么你们两周之内
again, you're not going
都见不到水
to see water for two weeks.
听到了吗
Hmm? ntendido?
他们抓到了惠斯勒
They got Whistler.
现在 由我决定
Now, I'll decide this
你什么都不能决定
You'll decide nothing.
你无权发表意见 勒齐
You can't deliver, Lechero.
你玩完了
You're done here.
然后呢?
Now what?
什么
What?
接下来怎么做?
What do we do?
你做的很好
You've been outbid.
等等 你在说什么
Wait. What are you talking about?
你在说什么
What are you ta ?
What are you talking ?
干的很好
That's, uh, very useful.
很好
Very useful.
惠斯勒是清白的
And Whistler's clear?
对
Yeah.
和天空一样清白 兄弟
Clear as the blue sky, brother.
喂?
Hello?
宝贝 是我
Baby, it's me.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我 我被吓到了 我一直在祈祷
Oh, I I've been so scared, I've been praying
每天都在
every day.
我也是 宝贝
I did, too, babe.
感谢上帝你没事
I just thank God youokay.
皮特打电话给我了 在他跟你说过话之后
Petey called me after he had talked to you,
他说你可能会回来?
and he said that you might be coming back here?
是我告诉他的
That's what I told him.
是的
Yeah.
你得小心再小心
You have to be so careful.
宝贝
Baby,
我一直在想
I've been thinking, and, um,
唯一的一件事 我
the only thing that I
我现在在乎的
that I care about right now
是你和孩子都没事
is that you and the baby are okay.
那就是我在乎的全部
That's all that matters to me.
我不会回来
I'm not coming back.
不是因为我不爱你 是因为
It's not because I don't love you, because
你知道我是真的
you know I do
真的爱你 胜过一切
I love you more I love you more than anything,
但是 我一直都让你伤心
but all I do is bring you down.
我对不起你
I'm no good for you.
不是 不是
That's not true, that's not true.
是的 是的 是的
Oh, it is, it is, it is, and
有时候 唯一的办法
sometimes the only way
去保护你爱的人
to protect the people that you love
是 是远离他们
is is by staying away from them.
等我解决了所有问题
one day, when i get my life together
不论多久 我都会找到你
however long that takes I'll find you.
我会找到你
I'll find you, and, uh,
我会让你和我们的孩子骄傲
and I'll make you and our baby proud.
我发誓
I promise.
我发誓 宝贝
I promise, my love.
我希望我们可以回到过去
I wish we could go back.
我会不惜一切的回到过去
I would give anything to go back.
我也希望
I wish that, too.
我也希望 宝贝
I wish that, too, baby.
我太爱你了 宝贝
I love you so much, baby.
我也爱你 宝贝
I love you, too, baby.
拜拜
Good-bye.
拜
Bye.
你知道的 他们告诉我你弟弟
You know, they told me that your brother
聪明过人
got all the brains,
但是我没想到你居然这么蠢
but I didn't realize you were this stupid.
你想干吗 苏珊?
What do you want, Susan?
我一叫你去实施计划
No sooner do I tell you to stick to the plan,
你就马上去找惠斯勒女友的麻烦
than you go and hassle Whistler's girlfriend.
你别再
You need to quit
弄的像个福尔摩斯 离她远点儿
playing Sherlock Holmes and leave her alone.
为什么?
Why?
因为是我说的
'Cause I said so.
-如何啊? -好
How about that? All right.
不如把枪放下 我好去做事
How about you beat it, so I can get to work?
我会的
I will
只要给我你从她那儿得到的东西
as soon as you give me what you took from her.
-我没拿她什么东西 -我有一加仑漂白剂
I took nothing from her. I got a gallon
一块防水布和一把钢锯(分尸用的) 在我车箱里
of bleach, a tarp and a hacksaw in the trunk of my car.
最多一小时
One hour, tops
你就人间蒸发了
you're off the face of the earth.
只是本关于鸟的书
It's just a bird guide.
我不会再问一遍了
I am not going to ask you again.
放下
Toss it.
明天 在酒吧
Tomorrow bar.
进展报告 我等你
Progress report. I will be waiting.
这是你要的水
So it's water you want.
你的水
Here's your water.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们要怎么出去?
So, how are we getting out of here?
不知道
I have no idea.